Radio voice: The first news is about support for the last two Windows 9x-
Radio voice: -operating systems, Windows 98 and Millenium Edition.
Radio voice: Support for the two operating systems will be dropping tomorrow,
98: Wait, what?!
Radio voice: and unfortunately, there is no option for paid extension of security updates.
Radio voice: Farewell, Windows 98 and Millenium Edition. Goodbye, 9x.
2000: What...
2000: Did I just hear?!
2000: I better go check on them.
2000: Right. I'm here.
2000: 98?!
2000: He's not responding...
2000: Let me go check the windows.
2000: What happened to him?!
2000: And the door's locked!
2000: You know what?!
2000: Finally.
2000: Just why?
Whistler: I forgot to watch the news today.
Whistler: Oh well...
2000: Whistler!
Whistler: ...
2000: What?
Whistler: What happened to 98?
2000: Have you not seen the news?
Whistler: I forgot to watch...
2000: 98 and ME are ending support!
Whistler: What?!
2000: And he's unconscious!
Whistler: I’ll get him in a ICU.
Whistler: Where is ME?
2000: I'll check on him now.
Whistler: Alright.
Whistler: I'll call the others.
2000: Got it.
2000: He's also unconscious...
2000: What's going on here...?
2000: I'm back.
Whistler: Don't worry about it.
Whistler: Thanks a lot for helping.
2000: Sigh.
2000: Just painful.
XP: I feel you.
2000: Can’t believe this happened today.
XP: Me neither.
2000: I just don't understand.
XP: Hey, look.
XP: They've both done a lot here.
XP: And Gates has some plans.
2000: Right...
2000: Hey, everyone.
2000: Let's go to the ICU.
XP: And Gates has some plans.
Whistler: Alright, so...
Whistler: We know the problem now.
2000: Will they be fine?
Whistler: Yeah.
Whistler: IE can explain.
IE 6: Their systems shut down.
IE 6: But their CPUs overheated.
2000: Ah...
IE 6: It’ll take quite a while to fix.
IE 6: The overheating damaged their CPUs.
XP: We're lucky this didn't happen at night.
2000: Yeah.
IE 6: We don't know when we'll be done, though.
IE 6: We've never had this issue before.
XP: Do you have an estimate?
IE 6: I'd say, roughly several hours.
2000: I hope we at least get to talk to them.
2000: Let alone, any of them...
Longhorn: I hope we do too.
Longhorn: All we can do is pray about it.
Whistler: Agreed.
XP: Let's face it.
XP: There’s nothing we can do about this.
2000: Sadly.
2000: I feel bad.
Whistler: Yeah...
2000: I wish I knew why.
2000: Why all this happened today.
XP: I also wish I knew, 2000.
XP: But guess what's better than this broken place.
2000: What?
XP: You guess it.
XP: If there was something better, it's above.
Longhorn: Don't worry about it.
Longhorn: We're told to live, so we do.
Longhorn: And Gates tells us the time to go.
Longhorn: This is just one of them.
Whistler: Agreed.
Whistler: They might miss us for the time being.
Whistler: But excitement awaits for them.
2000: ...
2000: Guys.
2000: You're all right.
2000: Let’s make it count.
Longhorn: Great motive!
XP: That's the spirit!
Whistler: Alright, I’ll call once we're done.
XP: Got it.
IE 6: Right, let's start working.
Whistler: Agreed, IE.
Longhorn: See you guys later!
IE 6: See you!
2000: I feel better now.
2000: Thanks a ton, guys.
XP: No problem.
Longhorn: Wait.
Longhorn: Where should we go now?
XP: Hmm...
XP: How about we go to your cafe?
2000: I think you've had too much of that.
Longhorn: Well, about the shop...
Longhorn: I closed it since I had to leave.
XP: Oh, right.
XP: Wait, did we miss someone?
2000: Who?
XP: Where's Ubuntu?
2000: Oh, wait.
Ubuntu 6.06 LTS: Guys?
2000: Hey!
Ubuntu 6.06 LTS: Sorry I got late.
Ubuntu 6.06 LTS: Had to take some time to close.
Ubuntu 6.06 LTS: I thought you were going?
2000: Yeah, we did.
Ubuntu 6.06 LTS: Ah, I see.
Ubuntu 6.06 LTS: How are they?
XP: Not good.
XP: Their CPUs overheated.
Ubuntu 6.06 LTS: ...
Ubuntu 6.06 LTS: What?
2000: Yeah...
2000: But don't worry about it.
2000: We're praying.
Ubuntu 6.06 LTS: Good to hear.
2000: Agreed.
XP: We're just roaming, by the way.
XP: Want to join?
Ubuntu 6.06 LTS: Oh, sure!
Ubuntu 6.06 LTS: I've got nothing to do, anyway.
Longhorn: Alright.
XP: Hmm...
XP: This looks promising.
Ubuntu 6.06 LTS: XP, this is where my store's at.
XP: Oh wait...
XP: I always walk through here!
Ubuntu 6.06 LTS: Haha.
Ubuntu 6.06 LTS: What were you thinking?
2000: Speaking of food...
2000: Is anyone getting hungry?
XP: Yes, I am.
Longhorn: Yes, I am.
Ubuntu 6.06 LTS: Haha.
Ubuntu 6.06 LTS: I have a suggestion for that, actually.
XP: What is it?
Ubuntu 6.06 LTS: Follow me.
Ubuntu 6.06 LTS: Here it is!
2000: Wait, what?!
XP: I've never been here before.
2000: Me neither!
Ubuntu 6.06 LTS: Really?
Ubuntu 6.06 LTS: Let's go in.
IE 6: Alright, all done.
Whistler: Good to hear.
Whistler: I'll go call the others.
IE 6: Alright.
Whistler: Alright.
Whistler: Hello?
XP: Hey, Whistler.
XP: How is it?
Whistler: We finished, but there's a setback.
Whistler: Can you come over?
XP: Sure.
XP: Just me or everyone?
Whistler: I'll need everyone here.
XP: Alright.
Whistler: Thanks!
Whistler: Hey guys.
Whistler: I’ve got some stuff to talk about.
XP: Yeah, you said.
Longhorn: How are they doing?
Whistler: Yeah, about that.
Whistler: 98’s conscious now, but…
2000: Wait, seriously?!
Whistler: Yeah.
Whistler: But he's paralyzed.
2000: Oh.
Whistler: ME still isn't conscious as well.
Ubuntu 6.06 LTS: They're going to be here, anyway.
Ubuntu 6.06 LTS: So I don't think it'd matter much.
Whistler: True.
2000: We also at least get to talk.
2000: Let’s hope the same for ME as well.
XP: Yeah.
XP: Let's hope.
Whistler: Let's go to the room.
XP: Yep.
98: Where are the others?
IE 6: They'll be here soon.
IE 6: Ah, here they are.
2000: 98!
98: 2000!
2000: I can't believe this.
Longhorn: Hopefully the same for ME now.
Whistler: Yeah.
XP: How are you now?
98: Exhausted.
2000: What even happened this morning?
98: I don't know.
98: I only remember yesterday, for some reason.
XP: You must've lost some memory.
98: Well, other than the fact I’m dying.
98: I see the monitor.
2000: Yeah...
98: Sigh.
98: You know what?
98: There’s no point in dreading.
98: If it's anything, it's a waste of time anyway.
98: Let's just get on with it.
2000: You're right.
2000: Let's make all this count.
Ubuntu 6.06 LTS: We don't have much time.
Ubuntu 6.06 LTS: A best to get what we have.
Ubuntu 6.06 LTS: Agreed?
XP: Agreed.
Longhorn: All the best.
Whistler: Right.
IE 6: All for it.
2000: Yep!
98: Wait...
98: Is that you, Ubuntu?!
Ubuntu 6.06 LTS: Yep, it's me.
98: Wow, thanks for coming over.
98: I’m sure you’re busy with your customers?
Ubuntu 6.06 LTS: Yeah, a lot.
Ubuntu 6.06 LTS: But I'm here for a reason!
98: Ah. Thank you.
Ubuntu 6.06 LTS: You're welcome.
ME: Huh?
ME: Where am I?
Whistler: Hey, you're awake!
Whistler: You're in the hospital, ME.
ME: Wait, why?
ME: Oh, wait...
ME: Is it about my support?
Whistler: Well...
Whistler: Yeah. Same for 98.
Whistler: How did you know?
ME: I just guessed.
ME: Takes little to know for me.
Whistler: I see.
ME: Oh well.
ME: I’m not surprised, to be honest.
2000: Hm?
ME: Let’s think about it for a second.
ME: At this point, I’ve done quite a lot.
ME: I say ahead there’s a send and receive.
2000: Ah…
2000: I see what you mean.
ME: Right?
ME: I’ve fulfilled my life at this point.
ME: After all, I can always watch.
ME: You know what Chicago does.
2000: ...
XP: ...
Whistler: ...
Longhorn: ...
Ubuntu 6.06 LTS: ...
2000: ...
2000: Thank you, ME.
ME: You're welcome.
Whistler: I’ve never seen confidence like this.
Whistler: All the time I thought death was a sorrow.
Whistler: But this is different.
XP: Me neither, Whistler.
XP: I’ve never seen anyone this brave.
Ubuntu 6.06 LTS: Well, let's cherish the moments.
ME: Indeed.
XP: We’ve got plenty of time.
XP: Let's keep talking!
Whistler: 25 seconds left...
98: Well, it's been fun.
Longhorn: We’ll join you guys later there.
98: Yep.
98: Thanks for everything!
2000: Same to you guys!
98: Ready, ME?
ME: More than ever.
2000: See you soon!
XP: We'll miss you guys.
98: See you!
98: Goodbye, world!